前面这段每集都有，我就不翻译了
相信大家可能就直接跳过去了
PRESIDENT REAGAN: Air and naval
forces of the United States
launched a series of strikes
against terrorist facilities...
REPORTER: Pan Am Flight 103 crashed
into the town of Lockerbie.
REAGAN: He has sanctioned
acts of terror
in Africa, Europe
and the Middle East.
PRESIDENT GEORGE HW BUSH: This will not
stand, this aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
REAGAN: This relentless
pursuit of terror.
PRESIDENT GEORGE W BUSH:
We will make no distinction...
REPORTER:
The USS Cole was attacked
while refueling in
the port of Aden.
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable
and cowardly act.
The next samba
we're going to swing for you
is one of the good old
favorites.
...until something stops him.
CARRIE: It was right
in front of my eyes,
and I never saw it coming.
MAN: That plane crashed
into the World Trade Center.
Thousands of people running.
We must and we will remain
vigilant at home and abroad.
(speaking Arabic)
SAUL: You're the smartest
and the dumbest fucking person
I've ever known.
CARRIE: I'm not the
one who got it wrong.
I'm the only one
who got it right.
SAUL:
Take 'em.
Take 'em all.
Homeland - 3x09
"Horse And Wagon"
前情提要也不翻译了，直接正文开始
Previously on Homeland...
I got plans for you.
What plans?
I'm gonna play you back
into Iran.
From now on, you work for us.
The Senator's made
some serious allegations.
That you had Majid Javadi
in a safe house
on American soil
and let him go.
We debriefed him, turned him.
He's ours.
I've made a decision to give
the marriage another chance.
_
(car door shuts) _
So I told him something
before you left...
about the Langley bomber.
You mean Brody.
No, that's just it.
It's not him.
The bomber's the only way
to prove that Brody's innocent.
Carrie, what the fuck
are you doing?
ADAL:
Carrie, turn around now.
This is your last warning.
(shouts)
Got a gunshot wound
to the upper left bicep.
significant bleeding.
Might have clipped an artery.
Where the fuck is Saul?
你醒了
You're awake.
我在哪？
Where am I?
海军医院
The Naval hospital.
在你中枪后，他们把你带到这里来的
They brought you here
after you were shot.
(呻吟)
(groans)
小心点，你不想把刚缝好的伤口撕裂吧
Careful, you don't want
to rip the sutures.
Quite a few of them.
恰好穿过，没伤着骨头
It was a through and through.
Missed the bone.
有一些肌肉和组织的损伤，神经无碍
Some muscle and tissue damage
but no nerve involvement.
你很幸运啊
You're lucky.
不，他是一个好的射手
No, he's just a great shot.
我在这里还得待多久？
How long will I be in here?
只要你还需要待在这里
As long as you need to be.
等我痊愈了呢
For me to heal
还是等CIA来处置我？
or for the CIA to figure out
what to do with me?
你得跟他们谈谈
You'd have to talk to them.
你知不知道你已经怀孕13周了？
Are you aware
you're 13 weeks pregnant?
是的，我知道
Yes.
孩子应该没事
The baby should be fine.
如果你想知道的话
In case you're wondering.
(开门，关门)
(door opens, closes)
瞳孔对光有反应
TURANI:
Pupils reactive to light.
血压60,40
MODARRES:
BP of 60 over 40.
太他妈低了
Too fucking low.
(虚弱地呻吟)
(groans weakly)
- 躺下
- Lay down.
- (嘴里咕哝着)
- (grunting)
他在飞机上开始戒毒
He started going
cold turkey on the flight,
所以，他们用半针管的
so they knocked him out
-伏特加控制住他
- with a half pint of vodka.
- 傻瓜们
- Idiots.
(groans)
MODARRES:
脉搏微弱
Pulse is thready.
(groans)
(yells)
放松
Take it easy.
我的东西在哪里，你们这些混蛋小偷们？
Where's my stuff,
you fucking thieves?!
*，我的东西在哪里？
Fuck! Where is my stuff?!
冷静，该死的！
Calm down, goddamn it!
(抽泣着)我的东西呢？
(sobs):
Where's my stuff?
别动
Don't move now.
你还有7天时间
ADAL:
You've got seven days till
Lockhart就要上任了
Lockhart's confirmed.
你觉得到那时，这个家伙会准备好吗？
You think this guy's
gonna be ready by then?
他不是我们想要的
He's not what we expected...
但是我们只有他了
but he's what we've got.
如果他答应做得话
If he agrees to do it.
他情况一团糟
He's a mess...
贫血...
anemic...
严重脱水，丙肝
severely dehydrated,
probably hep C.
HIV没有蔓延
HIV isn't a stretch.
如果你是说要去医院的话，那不可能
If you're suggesting a hospital,
it's out of the question.
我非常确定，我能让他保持稳定
I'm pretty sure
I can keep him stable,
但是这个家伙是有毒瘾的，sir
but the guy's a junkie, sir.
他得多久能好
How far is he into withdrawal?
还没开始
TURANI:
Hardly started.
他现在的情况
What he's feeling now,
会变得更糟
it's gonna get
a hell of a lot worse.
美沙酮能够缓解一些
Methadone would make it easier.
必须立刻戒毒
Has to be cold turkey.
不管怎样，我没得让他正常起来
Where he's going,
we need him functional.
即使这会杀死他吗？
Even if it kills him?
不会的
It won't.
因为你会让他活下来的
'Cause you will keep him alive.
明白吗？
Do you understand?
sir.
Sir.
(沉重的呼吸着)
(breathing heavily)
(干呕，恶心)
(retching)
(咳)
(coughing)
(喘气)
(panting)
你还好吧？
You all right?
哇哇！
Whoa, whoa!
停下来，你在干什么？
Stop!
What are you doing?
我需要它！
I need it!
你不能在用这个了
There's nothing there for you.
- 不，我现在很需要它！
- No, I need it now!
- 不
- No.
(西班牙语)给我，给我，给我...
(In Spanish) Give it to me,
give it to me, give me...
嘿，拿下它！
Hey, grab him!
针头在哪里？
Where's the needle?
- 找到了
- Got it.
- (sobs)
给他盖起来，躺下
Cover him up.
Stay down.
(wheezing):
Please...
感觉怎样？
How are you feeling?
医生说你恢复的不错
The doctor says
you're progressing nicely.
你马上就可以起来行走
You'll be up and walking
in no time.
但是，不能走出这里
Though, not necessarily
out of here.
外面有两个武装的保卫在门外
There are two armed guards
outside your door.
你知道，这从来都不能停止让我吃惊
You know it never ceases
to amaze me
你们这些人是怎么团结在一起的
how you people close ranks.
Here you are,
一次CIA行动的意外事故大错特错
a casualty of some CIA op
gone very, very wrong,
基本上是一个囚犯
basically a prisoner,
而且，不管怎样，我还是敌人
and still, somehow,
I'm the enemy.
你应该明白
You are aware
CIA没有被允许
that the CIA charter
does not include
在美国本土开展行动？
operations on US soil?
你知道，我在用止痛药
You know, I'm on painkillers.
我几乎不明白你在说什么
I can barely understand anything
you're saying.
好吧...
Well...
我看过你的资料
I've been going through
your file.
事实是，
The fact is,
你需要一个可以信任的人
you need someone you can trust.
为什么？
And why is that?
你被击中，躺在哪，你需要问一问
You're lying there shot
and you need to ask?
对你做出这一切的那个人
The man who did this to you,
他现在正在出去的路上
he's on his way out.
但是，我需要知道
But I need to know...
他去做什么？
what's he up to?
去问他吧
Ask him.
他在加拉加斯(委内瑞拉首都)做什么？
What was he doing in Caracas?
你甚至不知道他在那里，是吧？
You didn't even know
he was there, did you?
我刚从Carrie那里得到一条消息
I got another message
from Carrie.
她已经完全冷静下来了？
Is she calming down at all?
不，恰恰相反
No, the opposite.
参议院Lockhart刚才去看她了
Senator Lockhart
just paid her a visit.
不知怎么，他知道加拉加斯的事
Somehow, he knows
about Caracas.
这不可能
It's impossible.
他确实知道
Well, he does.
你认为他怀疑？
You think he suspects?
我确定他不知道一点线索
I'm sure he doesn't
have a clue.
但是她现在知道了
She does now.
那么，我们怎么办？
So what do we do about that?
和以前一样
Same as before;
让她在医院待着，继续看守
keep her under guard
at the hospital.
远离Brody
Away from Brody.
和Lockhart？
And Lockhart?
我不知道他到底怎么发现的
I don't know how
the hell he found out.
除了我们俩个，没有人知道
No one knew besides us.
我们的房子和办公室清扫了吗？
Have our houses
and offices swept.
每一个房间，从上到下
Every room, top to bottom.
发生了什么？
TURANI:
What happened?
拉到裤子上了
Shat himself.
天哪
Jesus Christ.
你是谁？
Who are you?
别说话
Don't talk.
你是军人，是吧？
You're soldiers, aren't you?
别说话
Don't talk.
烫死了，烫死了！
It's burning!
It's burning.
这不烫
It's not hot.
烫死了
It's burning!
(抽泣)
(sobs)
现在这种糟糕的情况，也许会更糟，可能还会持续3天，
TURANI: It'll continue as bad as
this, or worse, another three days.
而且至少一周后，
And at least a week after that
那些东西才能从体内排出来
before the stuff's out
of his system.
所以，你说的就是10天
So you're saying ten days.
我们只有6天
We have six.
而且，这一切结束后
Plus, at the end of all this,
他将变成一只虚弱的小猫
he's gonna be weak
as a fuckin' kitten.
还有一个选择
There is another option.
什么？
What?
(一种致幻剂，可以戒毒)
Ibogaine.
是从一种尼日利亚植物中提取的毒品
It's a drug based
on a Nigerian plant.
它能很快的加速恢复的过程
It dramatically accelerates
the withdrawal process
而且戒绝毒瘾
and kills the addiction.
副作用是残忍的
The side effects are brutal,
这就是为什么我们现在法律不允许使用
which is why
it's outlawed here.
恶心，呕吐，幻觉
Nausea, vomiting,
some hallucinations.
暴力的，
TURANI:
Violent,
离奇古怪的幻觉
mind-bending hallucinations.
有效吗？
Does it work?
有
ADAL:
It does.
听我的
Take my word.
(轻轻的哔哔声)
(beeping softly)
(哔哔声加快)
(beeping rapidly)
(哔哔声停止)
(beeping stops)
(歌声)
(quietly):
♪ From the halls of Montezuma ♪
♪ to the shores of Tripoli ♪
♪ we fight
our country's battles ♪
♪ in air, on land and sea... ♪
说点什么，****
Say something, you motherfucker.
别老站在那
Don't just stand there.
说点什么
Say something...
(轻轻抽泣)
(sobbing quietly)
(歌声)
MAN: ♪ First to fight
for right and freedom ♪
♪ and to keep our honor clean ♪
♪ We are proud
to claim the title ♪
♪ of United States Marine. ♪
Of United States Marine.
(抽泣)
(sobs)
(呻吟)
(moans)
哦...
Oh...
上帝...
God...
(moaning)
出去
Get out.
Get out!
(sobs)
你们给了我什么？！
What the fuck did you give me?!
(Brody sobs)
不...
No...
(咕哝声)
(grunts)
(both grunting)
给我那个！
Give me that!
滚开！
- (shouts in Arabic)
BRODY: - Get off me!
滚！
- Get off!
- (men shouting in Arabic)
滚开！
Get off of me!
滚！
Get off!
(speaking Arabic)
滚,不！
Get off me, no!
(speaking Arabic)
他马上睡着了
He'll sleep now.
得一会儿
For a while.
(叹息)
(sighs)
也许我们应该马上给Saul打电话
MAX: Maybe we should just
call Saul's landline,
打开化控开关
trigger the voice activation,
复查一遍我们的追踪程序
double-check our
tracking program.
我们可以
We could.
但是...？
MAX:
But...?
这个房子专线连接至
This house is leased to
一个特拉维夫市(以色列港市)运输集团
a shipping consortium
out of Tel Aviv.
- 这会让摩萨德(以色列情报机关)大篇幅报道的
- It's got Mossad written all over it.
MAX：- 是的
MAX: - Yeah,
但是如果这只是一个监视站呢
but what if it's just
a monitoring station,
或者一个秘密情报传送点？
or a dead drop?
那我们就浪费时间了
Then we're wasting
our fucking time.
(叹息)
(sighs)
看见这个了吗？
Are you gettin' this?
你还活着
You're alive.
那不是恩赐给你的
That wasn't a given.
想喝点水吗？
Want some water?
你为什么不把握丢在那里，让我死去？
Why couldn't you have just
left me there to die?
我认为你知道那根本就不是一个选择
I think you know that
wasn't really an option.
所以...
So...
(吞咽)
(swallows)
现在怎样？
what now?
那取决于你
That'll be up to you.
审判我？
A trial?
我没有做
'Cause I didn't do it.
你是说CIA爆炸的事？
You talking about
bombing the CIA?
我倾向于同意
I'm inclined to agree.
但你犯下的罪行不是从这个开始，也不是从这个结束(指：你犯的罪不只这些)
But your transgressions
don't begin or end there.
我会参与进一个来来回回
And I'm not about to engage
in a back and forth
最终不知怎么你成为受害者的事中
where you somehow
end up the victim.
我们俩个都知道你做了什么
We both know what you've done.
我们俩个都知道你是怎样的
We both know what you are.
一个挖了一个深坑把自己埋进去的人
A man who's dug himself
into a hole so deep,
常识都会告诉你，你没有出路了
common sense'd tell you
there's no way out.
我正在告诉你的是，可能还有出路
I am telling you, though,
that there might be.
如何？
How?
我给你一个机会
I'm offering you a chance
重新成为海军陆战队成员
to be a Marine again.
那个曾经的你
The man you were...
在你被摧残之前
before they broke you.
请别
Please.
(叹息)
(sighs)
不会了
No more.
我已经完了
I'm done.
你没有
SAUL (quietly):
You are not.
这将是你最的最后一件事
You will do
this one last thing.
不
BRODY:
No.
那么杀了我吧
So kill me.
现在就杀了我
Kill me now.
(咳)
(coughing)
你想死，是吧？
You want to die, huh?
(叹息)
(sighs)
我们走着瞧
We'll see about that.
(引擎转动)
(engine idles)
(引擎停止)
(engine stops)
把他扔下船去
AZIZI:
Put him overboard.
(grunts)
***，我马上下去
Fuck this shit.
I'm going in.
别，他会上来的
Don't. He'll come up.
我不相信
(whispering):
I don't believe this.
*！走
Fuck it.
Let's go.
(sputters)
拉他一下
Pull him...
(咳)
(coughs)
(coughing)
他像一块石头一样下去了
He went down like a stone.
完全没有尝试自救啊
No attempt to save
himself whatsoever.
现在他拒绝吃饭
Now he's refusing to eat.
强迫他吃
Make him.
你让我们怎么做
How do you expect us
to do that?
这叫做强行喂食
It's called
force-feeding.
恕我直言,sir
AZIZI:
All due respect, sir,
这家伙在这就是浪费空间
the guy's a waste of space.
现在，我建议不管你对他有什么想法
Now, I suggest whatever
you've got in mind for him,
还是放在6个月后吧
just push it six months.
让我们来处理好这件事吧
Let us do this thing right.
你让我照你想的做？
You done letting us in
on your thought process?
是的，sir
Yes, sir.
让他吃
Get him to eat.
他是对的，你知道
He's right, you know.
我们的窗户关得太快了
Our window's closing fast.
现在做不了就没有机会了，Saul
It's now or never, Saul.
(门关了)
(door opens)
(电梯铃声轻轻的响了)
(elevator bell dings faintly)
现在感觉怎么样？
How you feeling?
好像你真的在乎一样
As if you actually cared.
你知道，我在这里有时间思考
You know, I've had
time to think here.
我回忆这件事
And I keep coming
back to the fact
如果没有你的同意，我肩膀上
that this bullet in my shoulder
就不会有这颗子弹
would never have happened
without your okay.
你当时就快危害到整个行动了
You were about
to compromise the mission.
我就要为Brody洗白了
I was about to clear Brody.
你说你在后面
You said you were behind that.
“洗白Brody”
"Clear Brody."
这意味着什么？
What does that even mean?
所以你骗了我
So you lied to me.
我认为你不想来讨论
I don't think you
want to go there--
是谁骗了谁
who lied to whom.
Brody逃出这个国家
Brody slipping out
of the country
而你却昏迷14小时
while you were unconscious
for 14 hours.
你认为我曾经相信过这个吗，哪怕一秒？
You think I believed
that for a second?
你知道我在加拉加斯，你给我留了个消息
You know I was in Caracas,
you left me a message.
难道你不想知道他现在怎么样吗？
Don't you want
to know how he is?
他现在怎么样？
How is he?
他不太好
He's not well.
你们队他做了什么？
What did you do to him?
你知道，隐藏在这个问题背后的假设是
You know, the assumptions
behind that question
多么的令人误解，这让我害怕
are so misguided,
it frightens me.
我发现他非常不好
I found him in a bad way.
相信我
Believe me.
这不是我想要的
It wasn't something I wanted.
他在哪里？
Where is he?
在弗吉尼亚
In Virginia.
Dam Neck
At Dam Neck.
一个特殊行动小组正在让他恢复
Got a special ops team
trying to get him in shape.
恢复去做什么？
In shape for what?
这就是我想要谈一谈的
That's what I wanted
to talk about.
我有一个局
I have a play.
这关系到Brody
It involves Brody.
而且，我希望你能说服他
And I'm hoping
you'll convince him
这关系到每一个人的利益
it's in everyone's interest.
你跟我说Javadi是个局
You told me
Javadi was the play.
他是的
He is.
Brody是下一个阶段
Brody's the next phase.
你为什么需要我？
And you need me why?
我猜他已经拒绝你了
I'm assuming he already
turned you down.
我们还没有到那一步
We didn't get that far.
就像我说的那样，你情况不太好
Like I said, he's not well.
那么，你的想法是什么？
So, what is it?
What's your big idea?
Darnish Akbari
Darnish Akbari.
伊朗革命军的领袖
Head of Iran's
Revolutionary Guard.
是的
Right.
Javadi的上司
Javadi's boss.
同乡和平的唯一一个而且是最大的障碍
And the single greatest
impediment to peace.
我想让他消失
I want him gone.
(轻轻的笑)
(quiet laugh)
好吧，那祝你好运
Well, good luck with that.
Brody能够接近他
Brody can get to him.
怎样？
How?
作为兰利爆炸的作案者
As the Langley bomber.
Brody可以在那里寻求政治避难
Brody seeks political
asylum there.
得到Akbari的借鉴，把他带出来
Gets an audience with Akbari,
takes him out.
Javadi是他的继承人
Javadi's the heir apparent.
他走上王位，他就会从
He ascends the throne,
and he goes from being
伊朗最终要的20个人之一变成
one of the 20
most important people in Iran
最重要的3个人之一
to one of three.
只要他为我们工作
Only he's working for us.
Brody把他引出来？
Brody takes him out?
是的
Yes.
得了吧，Saul，你想的太多了
Come on, Saul, you're reaching.
Akbari的保护要比Ayatollah好得多
Akbari's better protected
than the Ayatollah.
Brody已经有非常娴熟的技巧能够进入一个严密的地方
Brody's got a knack for
getting into tight places.
他以前就这样做过
He's done it before.
这是一个自杀行动
At best it's a suicide mission.
不，他会有一个小队支援
No, he'll have a
team on the ground.
你想让我去说服他？
And you expect me
to convince him of this?
我希望你仔细考虑
I expect you to consider
deeply the upside
将美国的利益放在伊朗这条食物链的最高端
of placing a US asset
at the very top
of the Iranian food chain.
这才是我想要的
That's what I expect.
Javadi不能只是一个情报源
Javadi won't be just
an intelligence source.
他将掌管
He'll be in control
整个伊朗的安保
of the entire Iranian
security apparatus.
那不意味着他将违反之前的约定而装死
That doesn't mean
he'll roll over and play dead.
我知道
I know.
但是他可以做点什么的
But he can do something.
一些能打破这条长线的事
Something to break
the long jump.
一些战争之外的事
Something besides another war.
一些能够改变现实的事
Something that'll change
the facts on the ground...
这就够了...
just enough...
所以两个30年都没有能够交流的国家
so two countries that haven't
been able to communicate
for over 30 years
除了恐怖袭击和威胁
except through terrorist actions
and threats...
可以坐下来谈一谈
can sit down and talk.
就是这个局，Carrie
That's the play, Carrie.
告诉我这不值得浪费你的时间
Tell me
it's not worth your time.
(门关了)
(door opens)
(脚步声逼近)
(footsteps approach)
♪ ♪
(Brody深深的吸气)
(Brody inhales deeply)
(呼气)
(exhales)
嘿
Hey.
(叹息)
(sighs)
Brody，我想让你知道
Brody, I want you to know
知道今天我才知道你在这里
that I didn't know
you were here until today.
我一听说就来的
I came as soon as I heard.
告诉我，有没有什么我可以帮你的
Tell me if there's anything
I can do for you.
任何事
Anything.
(门开了)
(door opens)
(门关了)
(door closes)
你什么时候需要他？
When do you need him ready by?
这个月27号
27th of this month.
为什么这么早？
Why so soon?
那天是参议员Lockhart
It's the day Senator Lockhart's
上任听证会的日子
confirmation hearings begin.
好的
Right.
告诉我在加拉加斯发生了什么
Tell me what happened
to him in Caracas.
据我所知就是一团翔
A world of shit
as far as we know.
他在哥伦比亚的边境被枪击了
He was gut-shot
at the Colombian border.
差点死去
Nearly died.
我猜可能止疼药上瘾了
Got hooked on the painkillers,
I guess.
而且在清真寺还发生了意外
There was also
an incident at a mosque.
伊玛目和他的妻子被杀了
An imam and his wife
were murdered.
因为他？
Because of him?
是的，因为他
Because of him.
我需要一辆车
I need a vehicle.
你胳膊怎么了？
What happened to your arm?
滑翔运动时出现了意外
Hang gliding accident.
真的？
For real?
去你的CIA
Fucking CIA, Baraz.
你问她问题干什么？
What are you asking
her questions for?
就是说说话呗
Just making conversation.
下面左转
It's the next left.
现在怎么办？
What now?
等
Now we wait.
我们在房子旁待了24小时
We sat on the house
for 24 hours.
这是唯一一个出入的人
And this is the only person
who ever came in or out.
哦，天啊
Oh, Christ.
你认识他？
QUINN:
You know him?
是的，恐怕是
Yeah, I'm afraid so.
他是谁？
Who is he?
我妻子的一个朋友
A friend of my wife's.
他叫Alain Bernard
His name is Alain Bernard.
我妻子在孟买认识他
She met him in Mumbai.
他们在那里保持了一段时间的关系
They struck up
a relationship there,
现在可能还有，或者没有关系了
which may or may not
be ongoing.
我讨厌这样问，Saul
ADAL:
I hate to ask this, Saul,
但是你觉得Mira知道吗？
but do you think Mira's aware?
他是一个以色列的情报官
That he's an Israeli
intelligence officer?
不
No.
爱上这个家伙事她唯一的罪行
Falling for the guy is
her only crime.
你想让给我做些什么？
What do you want me to do?
现在？
For the time being?
把他抓起来
Pick him up.
放在一个黑洞里
Put him in a dark fucking hole.
那Lockhart怎么办？
ADAL:
What about Lockhart?
他怎么跟这些有关？
How does he fit
into the equation?
我想我发现了一个线索
I think I buried a lead.
什么？
Meaning what?
当我们这个家伙从安全屋离开的时候
After our guy left
the safe house,
我跟踪他去了Pete's Diner
I followed him to Pete's Diner,
国会山
Capitol Hill.
(wry laugh)
Dana？
Dana?
Dan...
嘿嘿嘿！
Hey, hey, hey!
嘿，***，让我出去！
Hey, assholes, let me out!
Brody...
放开我
Get off me!
哦，天哪
(grunting, muttering):
Oh... God...
- 让我出去！
- Let me the hell out!
- 放松
- Relax!
(grunts)
Brody!
***
Motherfucker!
Dana，是我！
Dana, it's me!
Dana!
- 回去...
- Get back...
- 放开我...
(growling): - Get off of me...
Dana!
*，Dana！
Fuck. Dana!
她听不见你的，Brody.
She can't hear you, Brody.
(喘气)：你...你个婊子
(panting):
You... you bitch.
你个***婊子
You fucking bitch.
(panting)
他在里面吗？
Is he in?
你预约和他见面了吗？
Is he expecting you?
Sir，你不能进去
Sir, you can't go in there.
那天晚上我要举办一个捐款活动
LOCKHART: I'm hosting a
fund-raiser that night anyway.
听着，我得挂了
Listen, I got to go.
怎么回事，Saul？
What the hell, Saul?
这是什么？
What is this?
打开
Open it.
有必要解释一下吗？
Care to explain?
Alain Bernard在帮我写一些简历
Alain Bernard is writing
a profile on me for Le Monde.
20分钟前
20 minutes ago,
Alain Bernard成人自己是
Alain Bernard admitted to being
以色列情报的线人
an asset
of Israeli intelligence.
那，我又为什么要关心这个呢？
And I should be concerned
about this... why?
因为，他声称他给了你一些信息
Because he claims he passed you
information obtained
这些信息是来自装在我家的窃听设备
from a listening device
planted in my home.
这简直荒谬！
That's preposterous.
是吗？
Is it?
一个电话给Benayoun大使，
One call to
Ambassador Benayoun,
这将是一个国际事件
it would be
an international incident.
再打一个电话给The Post
A second call to The Post,
然后你的照片将会是
and your picture'd be
on the front page
这个国家每一份报纸的头条
of every newspaper
in the country.
你想要什么？
What do you want?
时间
Time.
时间？
Time?
推迟你的让人？
Postpone your confirmation
直到下个月的中期
until the middle of next month,
然后这些将永远不会出现
and these'll never
see the light of day.
我不理解
I don't understand.
这是个非常简单的请求
It's a simple request.
再给我几周时间
Give me a few more weeks.
这不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.
你可以用这些击垮我
You could destroy me with this.
你可以保证你作为CIA头的任期
You could guarantee
your own tenure as director.
你为什么要让我摆脱这样的境地？
Why are you letting me
off the hook?
因为这将对我的妻子造成羞辱，参议员
Because it would humiliate
my wife, Senator.
而且会对局里造成伤害
And because it would
damage the Agency.
非常严重地
Badly.
那么我们达成协议了？
We have a deal?
是的
We do.
我希望你已经足够冷静来和我说话了
I was hoping you've calmed
down enough to talk.
Dana在一个前不着村后不着店的汽车旅馆做什么？
What's Dana doing
cleaning motel rooms
- in the middle of nowhere?
- 为什么？
- Why?
有什么不对的吗？
Is something wrong with that?
- 作为一个服务员？
- Being a maid?
- There's nothing
没有什么不对的，该死的，我就是想知道
wrong with that, goddamn it--
I just want to know
我女儿发生了什么！
what's going on
with my daughter!
喝吧，喝完我跟你讲Dana
Drink it, and I'll tell you
about Dana.
慢点，别犯恶心
Slowly, or you'll be sick.
好了
There.
怎么回事？
Now, what's going on?
Brody，她以前一阵子过得很不好
Well, she's had
a rough time, Brody.
她退学了
She dropped out of school.
从你们家搬出来了
She moved out of the house.
她改了她的姓
She changed her last name.
带我去那个汽车旅馆
Take me back to the motel.
不可能
That's not gonna happen.
看在上帝的份上，Carrie
For Christ's sake, Carrie.
我告诉过你了
I told you.
如果你还想再见着她，你就得...
if you want to see her again
you have to...
退出你的游戏吧，Carrie！
Quit your fucking games, Carrie!
我得亲眼看见她
I need to look her in the eye.
我想让她知道我是清白的
I want her to know
I'm innocent!
如果你继续喊的话，谈话就此结束
If you keep yelling,
this conversation is over.
仙子我想要让这两个人离开，
Now I would like
to tell these two men to leave,
可以吗？
can I do that?
(开门)
(door opens)
(huffs)
(关门)
(door closes)
你想要什么？
What do you want?
我猜和Saul说的一样吧
The same thing as Saul
Berenson, I'm guessing.
一些关于我再次成为海军陆战队成员的狗屎话？
Some bullshit about me
being a Marine again?
你想要什么，Brody？
What do you want, Brody?
一直以来，你想要什么?
What have you always wanted?
一个赎罪的机会
A chance at redemption.
最后一次告诉你，Carrie，炸弹不关我的事
For the last time, Carrie.
I didn't do the bombing.
你们都应该知道的
You of all people
should know that.
我不是说炸弹的事
I'm not talking
about the bombing.
我是说自杀背心的事
I'm talking
about the suicide vest.
我是说Elizabeth Gaines的死
I'm talking about the death
of Elizabeth Gaines
和那两个秘密特工的死
and those
two Secret Service agents
outside the State Department.
我在说在加拉加斯发生在伊玛目和
I'm talking about what happened
他妻子身上的事
to that imam and his wife
in Caracas.
做Saul让你做得事吧
Do what Saul is asking.
你让我做的？
- What you're asking?
是的，是我让你做得
- All right, what I'm asking.
不看在你的份上，看在Dana的份上
If not for your sake,
then for Dana's.
要不然的话，告诉她你是清白的只是
Otherwise, telling her
you're innocent is just...
另外一个谎言罢了
is just one more lie.
看着我，Carrie
Look at me, Carrie.
你现在不能派我出去为了一包香烟
You couldn't send me out for a
pack of cigarettes right now.
我们会帮你准备好的
We'll get you ready.
你需要做得就是愿意就好
You just have to be willing.
- (喘气)
- (panting)
- (indistinct chatter)
看呐，谁出来玩了
Well, look who's come
out to play.
BARAZ:
About fucking time.
得到妈妈的同意了吗？
Did you get Mommy's permission?
闭嘴，你们
Hey, shut the fuck up,
everybody.
我们要从这边走了
We're going this way.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
起来
Come on.
自己站起来
On your feet.
不，他得自己来
No.
He needs to do it by himself.
告诉我你什么时候能继续跑了
Tell me when you're
good to go again.
现在
Now.
走
Go.
16天后
找到马普托，莫桑比克
Find Maputo, Mozambique.
频率是多少？
What's the frequency?
KHZ 3265
KHZ 3265.
他们讲的是什么语言？
AZIZI: What language
are they speaking?
葡萄牙语
Portuguese.
底下的三张牌？
Bottom three cards?
梅花8
Eight of clubs.
(gunshot)
红桃10
Ten of hearts.
(gunshot)
黑桃J
Jack of spades?
拼出她的姓
Spell her last name.
Uh, B-A-C-Z-
E-W-S-K-I. Baczewski.
这里说她比谁更火辣？
BARAZ: It says here
she's hotter than what?
BRODY: - Georgia asphalt?
谁说的？
BARAZ: - And who said that?
Lula Fortune对Sailor Ripley说的
Lula Fortune to Sailor Ripley
in Wild at Heart.
对了！
Fucking-A right.
Yeah！
Yeah.
你们两个之间有什么吧？
So, you guys got
something going on?
没有
No.
得了吧
Come on, man,
我看见她在外面看你的样子
I've seen the way
she's checking you out
当你没有看见的时候
when you're not looking.
什么都没有
There's nothing.
真的？
Seriously?
真的
Seriously.
你不介意的话...
So, you don't mind if I...
if I hit that shit then, right?
看？是有什么的吧
(laughing): See?
There is something.
我知道的
I knew it.
没有的，继续吧，真的
No, go ahead. Really.
哦，我就是和你瞎说的
Nah, man,
I'm just fucking with you.
我结婚了
I'm married.
我们的第一个孩子刚出生
And, uh, we just had
our first kid.
是个男孩
It's a boy.
叫Devon
Name's Devon.
我怎么不知道？
How come I didn't know that?
只是...
Just...
我不喜欢谈论我的家庭
I don't like
talking about my family.
(敲)
(knocks)
迷信
Superstitious.
(筛子在桌子上滚)
(dice roll on table)
我们要开始了
Hey, we're on in five.
在指挥室
In the briefing room.
(sighs)
伊朗巡逻队在这个地区是断断续续的
Iranian patrols
in the area are intermittent.
但是他们训练有素，而且装备精良
But they are well-trained
and equipped.
而且，这里还有个空军基地
Also, there is also
an IRIAF base
70英里外
in Bijar, 70 miles away,
也就是说他们可以请求空军支援
which means they can call
in air support.
我们要谈论的计划是怎么样的？
AZIZI: What kind of
planes are we talking?
第一次海湾战争之后被留在伊朗的法国造的F-1
Uh, some French-built
F-1 Mirages impounded
from Iraq
after the First Gulf War
和6个中国的SU-24
and six Chinese SU-24s.
抱歉，我们能倒退一分钟吗？
Excuse me, can we back up
a minute?
当然
Sure.
这些人把握带到边境
The guys gets me
to the border...
然后我投降
where I surrender myself?
是的
Correct.
我们之所以选择Marivan是因为一些基地组织的指挥官
We chose Marivan because
several Al-Qaeda commanders
也是在那里请求政治避难的
also asked
for political asylum there.
我飞到Tehran之后呢？
What happens then?
I get flown to Tehran?
在一段时期的审查之后，我们是这么预想的
After a period of vetting,
yeah, that's our expectation.
好的，你是怎么觉得我能够距离
Okay, but what makes you think
I'll ever get close enough
Akbari足够的近并把他引出来？
to General Akbari
to take him out?
你将会得到像革命英雄一样的待遇
SAUL: You'll be treated as
a hero of the Revolution.
一些政坛的高层，像将军这样的，
The senior members of the
regime, like the general,
就会想利用你的宣传作用
want to take advantage
of your propaganda value.
加上Javadi会促成你和Akbari的会谈
Plus Javadi's on the ground
to facilitate a meeting
between the two of you.
但是如果我们不知道什么时候或者什么地点
But if we don't know
where or when
发生暗杀呢...？
the assassination goes down...?
你在考虑我们已经想好的计划了
You're concerned about
our extraction plan.
一旦行动完成，我们怎么把你弄出来？
How we're gonna get you
out of there once it's done?
是的
Yeah.
我马上就要说到了
I was just getting to that.
一旦你进入边境
Once you're inserted
at the border,
你队里的四个成员
four members of your team
将继续从南去Nodesheh
will continue south to Nodesheh,
在那里他们会穿过一座山，然后
where they cross the mountains
and make their way overland
到达Lavasan，这是Tehran外面的一个小城
to Lavasan, a small city
just outside Tehran.
反对派在那里会给我们提供一个
Opposition groups there
have provided us
安全屋
with a safe house.
我们已经先行动，
We've already gone ahead
做好了安全通信卫星的事情
and put in secure Satcom.
我们的暗号是...
Our code there is...
(speaking Persian)
你从什么时候开始抽烟的？
Since when do you smoke?
我没有
I don't.
I'm not.
只是看起来像我在抽烟
It just looks like I'm smoking.
(chuckles)
从没发生过
There.
It never happened.
你什么都没看见
You saw nothing.
什么都没有
Nothing.
看着...
Look...
我做了你让我做的
I did what you asked.
我正在做你想要我做的
I'm doing what you want.
你告诉过我要带我再去见一次Dana
Now you told me you'd
take me to see Dana again.
我的意思是等你回来
I meant after you get back.
得了吧，Carrie
Come on, Carrie.
我们都知道这次任务得很长时间
We both know
that's a long shot.
我们让它这么远
We made it this far.
是的
That's true.
我承认，我有我的疑问
I admit, I had my doubts.
什么？
Oh?
这就是你保持距离的原因吗？
Is that why you've
kept your distance?
嘿，没事
Hey, it's fine.
你配得上
You're entitled.
(sighs)
你6个小时候就要出发了
You're loading out
in six hours.
我不确定能不能带你离开基地又按时回来
I'm not sure I can get you off
the base and back in time.
看不见Dana我不不会离开
Well, I'm not leaving
until I see Dana again.
在那里，119
It's there. 119.
Brody，有一些事情你得知道
Brody, there's something
you need to know.
在她改名字之前
Before she changed her name,
在她离开家里之前
before she left home...
Dana在医院接受治疗
Dana was hospitalized.
爆炸发生两周后
About two weeks
after the bombing...
她曾试图自杀
she tried to kill herself.
谁？
DANA:
Who is it?
Dana，是我
Dana, it's me.
你爸爸
It's your dad.
(百叶窗沙沙响)
(blinds rustle)
(门栓打开)
(latch clicks)
Hi
Hi.
你是怎么找到我的？
How did you find me?
Carrie
Carrie.
我能进来吗？
Can I come in?
Dana，求你了?
Dana, please?
谢谢你
Thank you.
我必须见你
I had to see you.
好的
Okay.
你已经见了
You have.
噢，我的宝贝，对不起
Oh, my baby, I'm so sorry.
别这样
Don't be.
你现在怎样？
How are you now?
你为什么会在这里？
Why are you here?
我只是想告诉你，那些人说我做过的事情
I just wanted to tell you
that all those things
我没有做
those people said I did,
I didn't do.
好的
Fine.
好的，好的
Fine, good.
我没有杀那些人
I didn't kill all those people.
不是我
It wasn't me.
我没有
I didn't do it.
(sighs)
我马上就要离开了
And I have to leave soon.
几个小时后
In a few hours.
但是在离开之前我得来看看你
But I just wanted
to see you before I go.
你看到了
You did.
你有没有考虑过
Did you ever,
for one second,
我是不是想见你？
think about if
I wanted to see you?
你想听我说什么？
What... what do you
want to hear?
你是个好父亲吗？
That you were a good dad?
啊？
(sobbing):
Huh?
不管怎样，一切都OK吗？
That despite everything,
it's all okay?
你想让我说什么？
What do you want me to say?
看着
Look...
look, here...
就写在这里
here, just write it down.
真的，就写在这里，我会说给你听
Really, just write it down
and I will say it to you...
只要你保证
as long as you promise
我再也不会见到你
I will never have
to see you again.
你们两个
Either of you.
(sobs)
我会从Tehran回来的
I will come back from Tehran.
我知道你会的
I know you will.
不仅仅是为了她
And not just for her.
(car approaching)
你们去哪了？
Where the fuck were you?
他像谈一谈
He wanted to talk.
45分钟后就要出发了
He's got 45 minutes
to load out.
他准备就绪
He's all set.
你把他带离了基地
You took him off base.
他威胁要出去，Saul
He threatened
to pull out, Saul.
在外面任何事都可能发生
Anything could've
happened out there.
但是没有发生啊
But it didn't.
我真的对你失望
I am truly at
a fuckin' loss with you.
有点信心，Saul
Have a little faith, Saul.
两周前，没有行动
Two weeks ago,
there was no operation.
现在有了，都是因为我
Now there is, because of me.
我正想让你知道这点
I really need you to get that.
因为为了我们能够拿下这次行动，
Because in order for us
to pull this thing off,
我们得找个方式重新信任彼此
we're gonna have to find a way
to trust each other again.
或者至少相处一个不错的方法来假装
Or at least come up with a
really great plan for faking it.
♪ ♪
Brody...
那边再见
See you on the other side.
第一次做字幕，还请指正
新浪微博@核桃KD
All he has to do tonight is walk
across the border and ask for asylum.
And in the unlike event that
anything goes wrong?
We have it covered.
ON THE NEXT HOMELAND